{
    "subject": "resource/Jadranski_naftovod",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Jadranski naftovod (JANAF) is a crude oil transportation company in Croatia. It operates the JANAF oil transport system, a part of the Adria oil pipeline.JANAF operates oil terminal of the Port of Rijeka in Omi\u0161alj on the Krk Island. In 2010, the Port of Rijeka Liquid Cargo Terminal transported 6.4 million tonnes of oil, representing a 7% drop compared to 6.9 million tonnes transported in 2009. In 2010, JANAF recorded annual revenue of 464.9 million kuna (62.8 million euro), less than 1% down from 2009, and annual net profit of 118.5 million kuna (16 million euro), up 11% compared to the previous year. However, JANAF operations include other facilities and services besides the oil terminal concession in the Port of Rijeka. JANAF is a joint stock company owned by Croatian Pension Insurance Institute (50.5%), INA (16%), the Republic of Croatia (14.5%) and other shareholders owning less than 10% of stock each. JANAF chairman of the board is Dragan Kova\u010devi\u0107. JANAF had 380 employees working in Omi\u0161alj terminal and other JANAF facilities in Croatia.JANAF's share was listed as part of CROBEX before March 2011.",
    "human_readable": "Jadranski naftovod, also known as JANAF, is a crude oil transportation company based in Croatia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8246138095855713,
            "question": "What is the full name of Jadranski naftovod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6640490889549255,
            "question": "What type of company is JANAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6003509759902954,
            "question": "What does JANAF transport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.514337420463562,
            "question": "Where is JANAF headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49694913625717163,
            "question": "Is JANAF a public or private company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.448478639125824,
            "question": "What are some of JANAF's main services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4355059564113617,
            "question": "In which country is JANAF located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4170187711715698,
            "question": "Does JANAF have any subsidiaries or affiliated companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30058029294013977,
            "question": "What is the history of JANAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29898154735565186,
            "question": "Who are some of JANAF's major clients?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jadranski naftovod, also known as JANAF, is a crude oil transportation company based in Croatia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_888_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of JANAF?",
            "html": "dbpedia_888_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does JANAF have any subsidiaries or affiliated companies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_888_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country is JANAF located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_888_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_888_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that it does support the triple. Therefore, the answer is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention Jadranski naftovod as a crude oil transportation company based in Croatia, which aligns with the statement \"Jadranski naftovod, also known as JANAF, is a crude oil transportation company based in Croatia.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents confirm that Jadranski naftovod (commonly known as \"JANAF\") is indeed a crude oil transportation company operating in Croatia. The details about its operations, such as the Adria oil pipeline and contracts with other companies like INA-Industrija nafte, further support this statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}